Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Video and Film, 149315
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Original Material, 149418
    - [Animo; Bug; Little House], [1985]; 149463 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File MSS092_0379, Case 092.0381, Box PM 21, Cassette 092.0379, Box 111, Cassette ID: 092.0001)
      Format: 3/4" Umatic
    - [R+R/ Phil Zwickler], 1987; 149462 (Box 114, Cassette ID: 092.0077)
      Format: VHS
      Duration: [00:60:00]
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #1], 1989; 149461 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File MSS092_0036, Case 092.0434, Box PM 13, Cassette 092.0433, Box 110, Cassette ID: 092.0036)
      Format: Betacam
      Duration: [00:20:00]
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #2], 1989; 092.0037; 149460 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File MSS092_0037, Case 092.0437, Box PM 13, Cassette 092.0436, Box 110, Cassette ID: 092.0037)
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #3], 1989; 092.0038; 149459 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File MSS092_0038, Case 092.0440, Box PM 23, Cassette 092.0438, Box 110, Cassette 092.0038)
      Betacam, 20 min.
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0438).
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #4], 1989; 149458 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File MSS092_0039, Case 092.0443, Box PM 13, Cassette 092.0442, Box 110, Cassette 092.0039)
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0441).
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #5], 1989; 092.0040; 149457 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File MSS092_0040, Case 092.0446, Box PM 13, Cassette 092.0445, Box 110, Cassette 092.0040)
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0444).
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #6], 1989; 092.0041; 149456 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File MSS092_0041, Case 092.0449, Box 110, Cassette 092.0041, Box PM 13, Cassette 092.0048)
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0448).
    - Eleventh Hour - broadcast, [1989]; 092.0042; 149455 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File MSS092_0042, Case 092.0452, Box PM 13, Cassette 092.0450, Box 110, Cassette 092.0042)
      VHS, 30 min.
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0450).
    - [Interview w/ Artists Space and David Wojnarowicz], 1989; 092.0046; 149454 (Box 110, Cassette ID: 092.0046)
      Duration: 01:17:00
    - [Kitchen Tape 1 Production Element], [1989]; 149453 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0023)
      Duration: 00:37:01
    - [Kitchen Tape 2 Production Element], [1989]; 149452 (Box 110, Folder ID: 092.0027)
      Duration: 00:33:51
    - [Kitchen Tape 3 Production Element], [1989]; 149451 (Box 110, Folder ID: 092.0031)
      Duration: 00:57:44
    - [Kitchen Tape 4 Production Element], [1989]; 149450 (Box 110, Folder ID: 092.0035)
      Duration: 00:35:12
    - [ITSOFOMO #1], [1989]; 149449 (Box 110, Folder ID: 092.0051)
    - [ITSOFOMO #2], [1989]; 149448 (Box 110, Folder ID: 092.0052)
    - [ITSOFOMO #3], [1989]; 149447 (Box 110, Folder ID: 092.0053)
    - [ITSOFOMO #4], [1989]; 149446 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0055)
    - [ITSOFOMO #3 - Edit Master], [1989]; 149445 (Box 114, Cassette 092.0054, Box Digitized Access Copies, E-records 092.0054)
      3/4" Umatic, 35 min. 55 sec.
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0412).
    - [ITSOFOMO #4 - Edit Master], [1989]; 2018-01-27; 149444 (Box 114, Cassette 092.0056, Box Digitized Access Copies)
      3/4" Umatic, 32 min. 51 sec.
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0415).
    - [ITSOFOMO - Dat Xfer Workprint] (audio only), [1989]; 149443 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0057)
    - [Damned in the USA], 1991; 149442 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0080)
      Duration: [00:68:00]
    - [Marion - Tape #1 Master], [undated]; 149441 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0011)
      Duration: [unknown]
    - [Upstate w/ Marion Scemama], [undated]; 149440 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0012)
      Format: S-VHS
      Duration: 02:00:00
    - [Upstate], [undated]; 149439 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0013)
    - [Upstate Tape 2], [undated]; 2018-01-27; 149438 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0014)
      3/4" Umatic, 16 min. 48 sec.
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 1], [undated]; 149437 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0060)
      Duration: [00:21:00]
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 2], [undated]; 149436 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0063)
      Duration: [00:08:50]
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 1], [undated]; 149435 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0066)
      Duration: 00:22:17
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 2], [undated]; 149434 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0067)
    - [Lesbians, Globe Gun, Solar System, Indians, Ships...], [undated]; 149433 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0074)
      Duration: 00:31:56
    - [Project: Red, Hot and Blue], [undated]; 149432 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0075)
      Duration: 00:03:15
    - [Steve Brown/ David Wojnarowicz], [undated]; 149431 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0059)
    - [Decomposed Animal, Earthquake, Commercials, NEA Controversy], [undated]; 149430 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0078)
    - [G.I. Joe, Pulverizer, Robots, Evader, Arctic Blast], [undated]; 149429 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0081)
    - [Making Plaster Heads], [undated]; 149428 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0079)
    - [Son of Sam and Delilah], [undated]; 149427 (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0076)
    - [Plain Ants, Sex Ants, Target, Guns, Clock, Monkey, House... Bigots, Cathedral, Color American Flag], [undated]; 149426 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0003)
    - [Stock Images for Sec. III Performance], [undated]; 149425 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0004)
      Duration: 00:10:32
    - [Fireworks, Steer Wrestling, Wagon Wheel... Reagan, Bombs, Scorpion, Dust Feet], [undated]; 149424 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0006)
      Duration: 00:40:59
    - [Black and White, Flag at Night, Los Angeles Muscle, etc.], [undated]; 149423 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0002)
    - [Slowed Master], [undated]; 149422 (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0005)
      Duration: 00:20:23
    - [WOJO NEA #1], [undated]; 149421 (Box 110, Cassette 092.0043, Box Digitized Access Copies, E-records 092.0043)
      Betacam SP, 30 min.
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0453).
    - [WOJO NEA #2], [undated]; 149420 (Box 110, Cassette 092.0044, Box Digitized Access Copies, E-records 092.0044)
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0456).
    - [WOJO NEA #3], [undated]; 149419 (Box 110, Cassette 092.0045, Box Digitized Access Copies, E-records 092.0045)
      Preservation note: Digital access copy was migrated from Digibeta preservation master (Media ID: 092.0459).
    - [Kitchen Perf Tape I], [undated] (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0021)
    - [Kitchen Perf Tape II], [undated] (Box 111, Folder ID: 092.0025)
    - [Kitchen Perf. Tape III], [undated] (Box 110, Folder ID: 092.0029)
      General Note
    - [Kitchen Perf. Tape IV], [undated] (Box 110, Folder ID: 092.0033)
    - [ITSOFOMO - DAT Transfer], [1991] (Box 114, Folder ID: 092.0058)
      Duration: [00:49:00]
    - [David Wojnarowicz Super8mm Source Films - Tape 2], [circa mid-1980s]; ID: 092.0083; 149493 (Case 092.0083)
      Duration: 01:16:00
    - [David Wojnarowicz Super8mm Source Films - Tape 3], [circa mid-1980s]; ID: 092.0084; 149492 (Case 092.0084)
      Duration: 02:01:24
    - [David Wojnarowicz Super8mm Source Films - Tape 4], [circa mid-1980s]; ID: 092.0085; 149491 (Case 092.0085)
      Duration: 02:00:48
    - [David Wojnarowicz Super8mm Source Films - Tape 5], [circa mid-1980s]; ID: 092.0086; 149490 (Case 092.0086)
      Duration: 01:54:00
    - [David Wojnarowicz Super8mm Source Films - Tape 1], [circa mid-1980s]; ID: 092.0082; 149494 (Case 092.0082)
      Duration: 01:28:07
    - [David Wojnarowicz Super8mm Source Films - Tape 6], [circa mid-1980s]; ID: 092.0087; 149489 (Case 092.0087)
      Scope and Contents
      Telecine transfers of Super8mm films created by Wojnarowicz collaborator, Tommy Turner. Titles inlcude: Ass Kick', Roll 'CP', Dust Reel, A-PT. 2, Party Reel, Dog Head Reel, Maggot Reel, Hell Reel, Graveyard Ripoff, Donuts, Woji At Horror House, Cigarette Trick, Snow Fun At The Top.
      Duration: 02:01:00
    - [David Wojnarowicz Super8mm Source Films - Tape 7], [circa mid-1980s]; ID: 092.0088; 149488 (Case 092.0088)
      Duration: 00:28:00
  - Subseries C: Film - Access Copies, 149399
    - [Heroin - Unedited Color Footage], [circa 1979]; ID: 092.0175; 149400 (Reel 092.0175)
      Format: 16mm
      Footage: [290 ft.]
      Original Format:
      Description:
    - Heroin, 1981; ID: 092.0132; 149417 (Reel 092.0132)
      Footage: [92 ft.]
      Duration: [00:02:50]
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel III], [circa mid-1980s]; ID: 092.0203; 149416 (Reel 092.0203)
      Footage: [209 ft.]
    - [Mexico Film Footage II], [1983, 1986 as per Super8 edge code]]; ID: 092.0193; 149415 (Reel 092.0193)
      Footage: [179 ft.]
    - Mexico, etc... Peter, etc... [as per original container], [circa 1986, 1987]; ID: 092.0198; 149414 (Reel 092.0198)
      Footage: [405 ft.]
    - A Fire in My Belly, 1986-1987 (work in progress); ID: 092.0130; 149413 (Reel 092.0130)
      Footage: [470 ft.]
      Duration: [00:13:05]
    - [Mexico Film Footage], [1988 as per Super8 edge code]; ID: 092.0188; 149412 (Reel 092.0188)
      Footage: [736 ft.]
    - Beautiful People, 1988-1989; ID: 092.0164; 149411 (Reel 092.0164)
      Footage: [1400 ft.]
      Duration: [00:38:00]
    - Beautiful People - B+W Extras (Out-takes and Alt. Titles), 1988-1989; ID: 092.0166; 149410 (Reel 092.0166)
      Footage: [380 ft.]
      Duration: [00:11:00]
    - Beautiful People - Color Extras (Out-takes and Alt. Titles), 1988-1989; ID: 092.0168; 149409 (Reel 092.0168)
      Footage: [335 ft.]
      Duration: [00:10:00]
    - [Footage for Film About Peter Hujar], [undated]; ID: 092.0135; 149408 (Reel 092.0135)
      Footage: [600 ft.]
      Duration: [00:12:00]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 6 super 8mm rolls
    - Where Evil Dwells, [undated]; ID: 092.0139; 149407 (Reel 092.0139, Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0139)
      Footage: [1150 ft.]
      Duration: [00:28:00]
      Original Format: Super8mm film
    - [Howdy Doody #120], [undated]; ID: 092.0141; 149406 (Reel 092.0141)
      Footage: 330 ft.
    - [Howdy Doody #119], [undated]; ID: 092.0143; 149405 (Reel 092.0143)
      Footage: 659 ft.
    - [Howdy Doody #121], [undated]; ID: 092.0145; 149404 (Reel 092.0145)
      Footage: 706 ft.
    - [Swamp/Skeletons], [undated]; ID: 092.0169; 149403 (Reel 092.0169, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0169)
    - [Ants] (color), [undated]; ID: 092.0171; 149402 (Reel 092.0171)
      Duration: 00:08:00
    - [Driving, Sky, and Misc. Shots], [undated]; ID: 092.0173; 149401 (Reel 092.0173, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0173)
  - Subseries D: Film - Original Material, 149353
    This subseries contains completed works, works in progress, and source footage. Researcher access is limited to subseries C: Film - Access Copies. There may not be access material available for all original material. Please contact a Fales archivist for access.
    - Beautiful People, 1988-1989; 149398 (Reel 092.0106)
      Format: Super8mm
      Footage: 504 ft.
    - Beautiful People - Out-takes (color), 1988-1989; 149397 (Case 092.0107)
      Footage: [66 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 3 Super8mm rolls
    - Beautiful People - Out-takes and Alt. Titles (B+W), 1988-1989; 149396 (Case 092.0108)
      Footage: [134 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 4 super8mm rolls
    - Beautiful People - Alt. Titles (color), 1988-1989; 149395 (Case 092.0109)
      Footage: [65 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 2 super8mm rolls
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel], [1988 as per edge code]; 149394 (Case 092.0110)
      Footage: [363 ft.]
    - [Mexico Film Footage], [1988 as per edge code]; 149393 (Case 092.0111)
      Footage: 386 ft.
    - [Mexico Film Footage II], [1983, 1986 as per edge code]; 149392 (Case 092.0112)
      Footage: 74 ft.
    - Mexico, etc... Peter, etc... [as per container], [circa 1986, 1987]; 149391 (Case 092.0113)
      Footage: [225 ft.]
    - Fear of Disclosure, The Psycho-social Implications of HIV Revelation, 1988; 149390 (Reel 092.0114)
      Footage: [210 ft.]
      Duration: [00:05:00]
    - Where Evil Dwells - Camera Original I, [undated]; 149389 (Case 092.0115, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0115)
      Footage: [400 ft.]
    - Where Evil Dwells - Camera Original II, [undated]; 149388 (Case 092.0116, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0116)
    - [New York Cultural Centre Annex Performance], [undated]; 149387 (Case 092.0117, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0117)
      Footage: 263 ft.
    - [Rolls 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8], [undated]; 149386 (Case 092.0118, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0118)
      Footage: 401 ft. 49 frames
    - [Rolls 9,10,11], [undated]; 149385 (Case 092.0119, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0119)
      Footage: 149 ft. 70 frames
    - [Rolls 17,18,19], [undated]; 149384 (Case 092.0120, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0120)
      Footage: 150 ft. 46 frames
    - [Anti-Gay Bigots, Misc Footage], [1986 as per edge code]; 149383 (Case 092.0121, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0121)
      Footage: 149 ft.
    - [Frog Dance, etc.], [undated]; 149382 (Reel 092.0122, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0122)
      Footage: 522 ft.
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel III], [circa mid-1980s]; 149381 (Case 092.0123)
      Footage: 93 ft. 35 frames
    - A Fire in My Belly, [circa 1985]; 149380 (Case 092.0124)
      Footage: 262 ft. 24 frames
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel], [late 1980s]; 149379 (Case 092.0125, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0125)
      Footage: 206 ft. 65 frames
    - [Howdy Doody Footage I], [undated]; 149378 (Case 092.0126)
      Footage: 360 ft. 66 frames
    - [Howdy Doody Footage II], [undated]; 149377 (Case 092.0127)
      Footage: 202 ft.
    - [Howdy Doody Footage III], [undated]; 149376 (Case 092.0128)
      Footage: 388 ft.
    - Heroin, 1981; 149375 (Case 092.0133)
      Footage: 51 ft.
    - [Peter Hujar - Rolls], [undated]; 149374 (Case 092.0136)
      Footage: [350 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 6 super8mm rolls
    - [Heroin - Unedited Color Footage], [circa 1979]; 149373 (Case 092.0146)
      Footage: [340 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 7 super8mm rolls
    - [Cockfights], [1986]; 149372 (Case 092.0147, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0147)
      Footage: [175 ft.]
    - [Out Sarah's Window; Demolition Derby], [undated]; 149371 (Case 092.0148, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0148)
    - [Nature, Water, Swamp], [1987]; 149370 (Case 092.0149, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0149)
      Footage: [425 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 9 super8mm rolls
    - [Rain/Mammals], [1981,1987]; 149369 (Case 092.0150, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0150)
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 10 super8mm rolls
    - [Gorillas, Elephants, Waves, Sky], [1986,1987]; 149368 (Case 092.0151, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0151)
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 7 super8mm rolls]
    - [Cavern Point/Driving Shots], [1987, 1983]; 149367 (Case 092.0152, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0152)
      Footage: [275 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 5 super8mm rolls
    - [Misc. B+W Shots], [1983,1986,1987]; 149366 (Case 092.0153, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0153)
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 8 super8mm rolls
    - [Ants] (color), [1986,1987,1988]; 149365 (Case 092.0154)
      Footage: [160 ft.]
    - [Swamp/Skeleton] (color), [1985, unknown]; 149364 (Case 092.0155)
      Footage: [240 ft.]
    - [Driving, Sky, and Misc. Shots], [undated]; 149363 (Case 092.0156)
    - [Fire Boys, Ants, and Mexico Themes], [1981,1984,1986,1987]; 149362 (Case 092.0157, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0157)
      Footage: [300 ft.]
    - [Unidentified Film w/ David Wojnarowicz], [undated]; 149361 (Reel 092.0158)
      Footage: 128 ft.
    - [Nite Scenes w/ David W.(Neg); Centaur Films], [undated]; 149360 (Reel 092.0159)
      Footage: 102 ft. 6 frames
    - Manhattan Love Suicides, 1984; 149359 (Box 113, Folder ID: 092.0212)
      Format: [Super8mm]
      Footage: [unknown]
      Description: Featurette
    - [Aeroport/ Train Lines/ Gary/ Rail Landscapes/ Bercy] (undeveloped film reel), [undated]; 149358 (Box 113, Folder ID: 092.0213, Box Digitized Access Copies, File mss092_0213)
    - [Crows] (undeveloped film reel), [undated]; 149357 (Box 113, Folder ID: 092.0214)
    - [Bercy Windows, Stones/ Fire] (undeveloped film reel), [undated]; 149356 (Box 113, Folder ID: 092.0215)
    - [A) Morphologies, Restaurant Cafe 2] (undeveloped film reel), [undated]; 149355 (Box 113, Folder ID: 092.0216)
    - [B) Morphologies, Restaurant Cafe 2] (undeveloped film reel), [undated]; 149354 (Box 113, Folder ID: 092.0217)
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 90, undated; 191830 (Box 90)
      092.0106-092.0123
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 91, undated; 191831 (Box 91)
      092.0124-092.0128, 092.0133, 092.0136, 092.0146-092.0149 C
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 92, undated; 191832 (Box 92)
      092.0149 D-092.0154
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 93, undated; 191833 (Box 93)
      092.0155-092.0157, 092.0160, 092.0162, plus 7 unnumbered folders
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 94, undated; 191834 (Box 94)
      (Trailer) 1986, N.Y.C, D. Wojnarowicz 228-7024; 092.00158-092.0159 "Nite Scenes w/ David W.; Envelope For Film, "Kin-O-Lux, Inc. - David Wojnarowicz"
    - Lists and notes on film and video content (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Subseries E: Commercial Works by Others, 149316
    - Anita Dances of Vice, by Rosa von Praunheim, VHS tape (Dub), undated; 149352 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Bayard Rustin, by Phil Zwickler, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149351 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - The Critical Years / The Grace of God, by Gerald Lecuyer, 40 min. VHS tape (dub), undated; 149350 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Excerpts from: Blind Prosperity / Money Talk, by Gloria McLean & Ben Neill, Teliospore, by Gloria McLean, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149349 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Fedora / Laura, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149348 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Fingered, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, undated; 149347 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Game Set Match, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149346 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Genet / Harvey Milk, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149345 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes, Twentieth Century Fox, VHS tape, undated; 149344 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - How to Marry a Millionaire, Twentieth Century Fox, VHS tape, undated; 149343 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - How to Shoot a Crime, by Kraus, (Chris?) 26 min. VHS tape, undated; 149342 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - La Belle et La Bete / Visages de Femmes, VHS tape, undated; 149341 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - La Dolce Vita, Pt. I, by Federico Fellini, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149340 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - La Dolce Vita, Pt. II, by Federico Fellini, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149339 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Lawrence of Arabia, Columbia Pictures, Pts. 1-2, 2 VHS tapes, undated; 149338 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Manhattan love Suicides w/ Bill Rice & D. Wojnarowicz, b&w, 30 min. VHS tape, undated; 149337 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Maria Callas: Hamburg Concert 1959, Kuktur, VHS, 149336 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Mondo Cane / Macbeth (Kurosawa) / Sting in Tokyo, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149335 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Mother Theresa, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149334 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Mr. Hulot's Holiday, by Jacques Tati, & other video, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149333 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Never on Sunday, MGM, UA, VHS tape, undated; 149332 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Pursuit of Happiness (Malle) / La Strada / Stranger Than Paradise, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149331 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Quilt, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149330 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - The Red Hot Organization / No Alternative, Nov 1993, VHS tape (dub), 149329 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Red Hot & Blue: A Tribute to Cole Porter to Benefit AIDS Research and Relief, Arista, 1990, VHS tape, 149328 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Rev. Howard Finster, Man of Vision, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149327 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - The Right Side of My Brain, by Richard Kern, 30 min. VHS tape, undated; 149326 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Rumblefish, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149325 (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Sex vs. Guns, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, undated; 149324 (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - Stop the Church, by Robert Hilferty, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149323 (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - Submit to Me / Death Valley '69 / You Killed Me First, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, 1969; 149322 (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - Submit to Me / Death Valley '69 / You Killed Me First, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, 1969; 149321 (Box 97, Folder 32)
    - Tom Rubnitz, Video Director: various, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149320 (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - A Virus Knows No Morals, by Rosa von Praunheim, First Run Features, 84 minute VHS tape, undated; 149319 (Box 97, Folder 34)
    - Where Evil Dwells, by Wojnarowicz & Turner, VHS tape (dub), undated; 149318 (Box 97, Folder 35)
    - The Young Ones (various series episodes), VHS tape (dub), undated; 149317 (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - Subseries F: Commercial Audiotapes, 149980
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; 149987 (Box 20, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; 149986 (Box 21, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; 149985 (Box 22, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; 149984 (Box 23, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; 149983 (Box 24, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; 149982 (Box 25, Folder no number)
    - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated; 149981 (Box 26, Folder no number)
- Series XI: Art Works, 149141
  - Subseries A: Finished/Original, 149271
    - Art - blue ballpoint pen drawing - "Look Honey a Hallucination", undated; 149306 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Art - color separation, undated; 149314 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Art Sketch Book - "Bowery Joe", undated; 149313 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Art - 2 prints - Brain-Time, undated; 149312 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Art - production - color sample - The Death of American Spirituality, undated; 149311 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Art - production - color separation - The Death of American Spirituality, undated; 149310 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Art - black ink, undated; 149309 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Art - frottage, undated; 149308 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Art - images and text, undated; 149307 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Art - "Mexico" collage, undated; 149304 (Box 148, Folder 9B.)
    - Art - "I Have Always Liked...the Idea of Movies. .", undated; 149303 (Box 148, Folder 9C.)
    - Art and Images - Memories that Smell Like Gasoline, undated; 149302 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Art and Poem - graphite pencil drawing of dog with cast, undated; 149301 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Art - Peter Hujar's diagnostic letter altered with a drawing of two men kissing, from W's "Fuck You Faggot-Hater" series, undated; 149300 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Art - transparency, "Buying Souls. .", undated; 149299 (Box 148, Folder 12A.)